CC
***W A R N I N G***
THIS IS A PRIVATE COMPUTER SYSTEM.
This computer system including all related equipment, network devices, are provided only for authorized use.
All computer systems may be monitored for all lawful purposes, including those activities that are authorized for management of the system.
All information including personal information, stored or sent over this system may be monitored.
Uses of this system, authorized or unauthorized, constitutes consent to monitoring of this system.
Unauthorized use may subject you to criminal prosecution.
WARNING: Unauthorized access to this system is forbidden and will be prosecuted by law.
By accessing this system, you agree that your actions may be monitored.

alln01-oob-sw2#t
